Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Aleppo Series (Box 6)
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref906; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref907; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref908; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.9 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape., Circa 1930-1950; ref909; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of men conversing in a car., Circa 1930-1950; ref910; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 7.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Cars/Trucks; Men; Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref911; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman outdoors., Circa 1930-1950; ref912; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a man (linked ref912)., Circa 1930-1950; ref913; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman with two dogs on a leash in the snow., Circa 1930-1950; ref914; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Snow; Cars/Trucks; Dogs; Individual Portraits; Animals; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An individual portrait of a woman with a headscarf smoking., Circa 1930-1950; ref915; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Smoking; Cigarettes; Head Covers/Veils; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman (linked ref915)., Circa 1930-1950; ref916; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 7.9 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a woman on horseback., Circa 1930-1950; ref917; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Women; Animals; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref918; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Airplanes; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref919; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An interior of a room with a radio, map, and golf clubs., 1944-1945; ref920; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Golf; Radios; Maps; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref921; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref922; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Photographic Prints; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref923; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.8 x 7.9 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Buildings; Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An aerial landscape of a section of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref924; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref925; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref926; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.9 x 8.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - A portrait of a man standing next to the "Southern Star" airplane in a field., Circa 1930-1950; ref927; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.8 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Airplanes; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; English Writing
  - An individual portrait of a man smoking next to an airplane., Circa 1930-1950; ref928; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Men; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref929; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.7 cm (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref930; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Buildings; Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of two people on horseback., Circa 1930-1950; ref931; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8.7 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Men; Women; Horses; Animals; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref932; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref933; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.9 x 7.9 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref934; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Airplanes; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref935; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Buildings; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref936; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref937; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Airplanes; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref938; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref939; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Buildings
  - An individual picture of a man on horseback jumping a hurdle., Circa 1930-1950; ref940; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Men; Aleppo, Syria; Animals; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref941; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 18 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Hats; Aleppo, Syria
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref942; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Women; Hats; Clocks/Watches; Aleppo, Syria; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref943; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Hats; Jewelry; Women; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref944; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.6 x 17.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref945; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Women; Hats; Aleppo, Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat and eating., Circa 1930-1950; ref946; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.7 x 17.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Women; Hats; Food; Jewelry; Aleppo, Syria; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - An individual portrait of a woman wearing a hat., Circa 1930-1950; ref947; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 31.2 x 20.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Studio Series II (Box 7)
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing a scarf., Circa 1960-1975; ref948; Armous Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Women; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 951, 952, 970, 971, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 1972; ref949; Studio Damashk, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy with his hand on his face., March 1966; ref950; Studio Echbelia, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing glasses (linked ref 949, 952, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 28 October 1962; ref951; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing glasses (linked ref 949, 951, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 28 October 1962; ref952; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1960-1975; ref953; Studio Fardosse, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Children
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1960-1975; ref954; Studio Fardosse, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 12 August 1960; ref955; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 6.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 13 October 1970; ref956; Studio Al Qusour, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Facial Hair; Men
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., Circa 1960-1975; ref957; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.4 x 3.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a girl wearing a patterned dress., 26 March 1966; ref958; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.1 x 5.9 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Damascus, Syria; Girls; Children; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a man., 9 October 1962; ref959; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of a boy and a baby., Circa 1960-1980; ref960; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 7 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 12 March 1964; ref961; Studio Star, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Damascus, Syria; Facial Hair; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing glasses with a mustache., 22 April 1982; ref962; Studio Star, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.9 x 7 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of two men., March 1962; ref963; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8 x 6.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1954; ref964; Photo Katchadour, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy holding a candle and a book., Circa 1960-1980; ref965; Photo Mohammad, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Aleppo, Syria; Religion; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of two boys holding hands., 6 June 1974; ref966; Photo Liban, Beirut, Lebanon; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.9 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Beirut, Lebanon; Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of two women., Circa 1960-1980; ref967; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Syria; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of four children and a votive statue of Mary., Circa 1960-1980; ref968; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 8.7 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Children; Religion; Toys; Churches; Boys; Girls; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a woman and a man., 1954; ref969; Photo Liore, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Aleppo, Syria; Men; Women; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Armenian Writing; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 949, 971, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., Circa 1970-1975; ref970; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 949, 970, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 22 August 1973; ref971; Studio Damashk, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 6.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a man (949, 970, 971, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 8 September 1963; ref972; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing leather jacket (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 15 February 1967; ref973; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 6 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 27 March 1968; ref974; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a man (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 27 March 1968; ref975; Photo Boyadjian, 65 Avenue Barada, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.4 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Men
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing leather jacket (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 982, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 15 February 1967; ref976; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4.1 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man., June 1954; ref977; Photo Paroun, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.6 cm (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a woman., Circa 1960-1980; ref978; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Women; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1950-1970; ref979; Studio Star, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Men; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a baby boy., 27 December 1955; ref980; Photo Kriko, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Aleppo, Syria; Armenian Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy holding a bible and wearing a rosary., 15 June 1962; ref981; Studio Jack, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.5 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Religion; Books; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Boys; Children; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a leather jacket (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 983, 984, 986, 987)., 15 February 1967; ref982; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4.2 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a leather jacket (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 984, 986, 987)., 15 February 1967; ref983; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a leather jacket (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 986, 987)., 15 February 1967; ref984; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.3 cm (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 3 February 1954; ref985; Photo Katchadour, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; French Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 972, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 987)., 1961; ref986; Studio Mallouhy, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy (linked ref 949, 970, 971, 973, 974, 975, 976, 982, 983, 984, 986)., 1961; ref987; Studio Mallouhy, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing tinted glasses., 20 March 1961; ref988; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Damascus, Syria; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., Circa 1950-1975; ref989; Studio Mallouhy, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
- Studio Series III (Box 8)
  - A team portrait of a girls' basketball team (linked ref991)., 4 March 1976; ref990; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Girls; Children; Students; Sports; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Women; Men
  - A team portrait of a girls' basketball team (linked ref990)., 4 March 1976; ref991; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Students; Girls; Children; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of a girls' sports team., Circa 1976; ref992; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Girls; Students; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Children; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of a girls' sports team., Circa 1976; ref993; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Girls; Students; Children; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of a children's swim meet (linked ref995)., September 1975; ref994; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Swimming; Swimming Pools; Children; Boys; Girls; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Sports
  - A group portrait of a children's swim meet (linked ref994)., September 1975; ref995; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 1)